My uncle bought a bull pizzle on the street
But he doesn't know how to cook it
Since I have some time right now...
Gonna cook this thing for everyone to enjoy
Uncle how'bout cook the pizzle with chili?
Sure thing!
Pizzle won't taste good without chili
The more spicy, the better
Got it!
Add more chili, especially Qixing Jiao(Seven Star Pepper) which enhances the spiciness
Or you ain't cover the odor
My uncle probably froze this for several days
Only fresh pizzle tastes good, but a short time in the fridge won't matter that much after all
Blanching first, then we can peel this part off
cut it open to wash the interior
Ginger & Garlic
Well, gonna come back to prepare the garlics
Qierwa
Can you start the fire for us?
Coming now!
Throw it in the wok for blanching
After that we can wash it thoroughly
Actually it's good for women's body as well despite being labeled as a masculine food
Alright it's done blanching, let's drain the water and take some time to clean it
It shrinks quite a bit
There is only a fraction of it left comparing to its size before
See
Let's cut it before taking out for the final sanitation
Peel the fat off
And also clean the connective tissues which makes the pizzle stinky
Cut the pizzle into small segments, set aside
Tilt the knife and cut the garlic sprouts into small segments, set aside
Dice a small chunk of hot pot condiment, set aside
Slap the ginger with knife and mince it, set aside
Finely dice some garlics and set aside
Ayo, It is uncle that can do this after all
I am a fire-making veteran
Qierwa took her time yet still fail to start the fire
Make sure that you got all the seasonings
Use quality stuff instead of those cheap knock off
You need good stuff, and this is exactly what you need
I hand-picked the appropriate ones
Uncle did you know that pork price skyrocketed recently
ye, exponential increases
Port sells at 35 yuan per jin in Chen Du, Chong Qiu
How much?
35 yuan per jin(250g)
But I did not see you selling port these days?
No
Gonna do when it makes money
Make it spicy, remember
Adding oil now
Do it
I'm dropping my "Kuan You"(lit lots of oil)
Sure, pizzle needs Kuan You
Add more Sichuan Peppercorn as well
Definitely
Add more chili n. paper to cover the odor
I also put quite a lot of picked chili
Spicy and numbing is the best taste profile for this dish
I used hot pot condiments for seasoning
Good
Lowering the heat, uncle
Emm, already smiling the fragrance
You need quality Kuan You to cook the dish
You don't get the the fragrance no matter how hard you try unless you use good Kuan You
That's why I can sell my Kuan You well at the price of 10 yuan per Jin
It is just that!
oops
20 minutes would be enough cooking it with the lid on
Well we actually have braised it for nearly 40 minutes
I tried it at the 20 minutes point
I can chew through but I was afraid that my uncle won't make it, so I braised it for some extra time
After 40 minutes...
Inaudible
I prepared some garlic sprouts to lay on the bottom of the pot
These are raw
Because we are suppose to heat it on the stove again later
This dish is suitable for winter
Let me get the seasoning done first
We only need to add soy sauce since I used hot pot condiments
Then put the garlic sprouts in
It's an OK when garlic sprouts are cooked
Alright, ready to serve
It must be a tasty dish!
The stove at bottom is filled with charcoal
which heats up the dish on the top slowly
while we are eating
Aunt is cooking some greens
There are few people who can cook pizzle properly
It is actually quite simple
Try it! Uncle
Let me check on your skills
Then I used hot pot condiments to cook the dish
So I did not add any extra salt but only a bit of soy sauce
After that you add garlics, pickled chili, ginger
And laying some garlic sprouts for the final step
Those sprouts will get slowly cooked
which increases the flavor during the process
Wow, it's both spicy and numbing
Try it?
I'm waiting for Auntie to finish cooking the greens
Spicy and numbing
Almost like "Mala Hot Pot"
Everyone please don't misinterpret pizzle as a soup-only ingredient
You can use it to make soup
Other than that, you can braise it with chili or without chili
All good
The general conception is that pizzle is good for man
While in truth it is also good for woman to have
Alright, this is it for today because it's dining time for us
So apparently all you will eat is greens?
Exactly